<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>YAML Schemas on Dynamic Simulation Environment</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/</link><description>Recent content in YAML Schemas on Dynamic Simulation Environment</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Schema: Manifest</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/manifest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/manifest/</guid><description>(v0.0.1)
Manifest kind: Manifest metadata: name: string labels: property1: string property2: string annotations: property1: string property2: string spec: repos: - name: string repo: string path: string registry: string user: string token: string tools: - name: string version: string repo: string arch: - string schema: string models: - name: string version: string repo: string arch: string schema: string channels: - name: string alias: string expectedModelCount: 0 selectors: property1: string property2: string annotations: property1: string property2: string simulations: - name: string parameters: transport: redispubsub environment: property1: string property2: string files: - name: string uri: string repo: string processing: string generate: string modelc: true models: - name: string model: string channels: - name: string alias: string expectedModelCount: 0 selectors: property1: string property2: string annotations: property1: string property2: string files: - name: string uri: string repo: string processing: string generate: string modelc: true documentation: - name: string uri: string repo: string processing: string generate: string modelc: true This schema object defines a Manifest kind.</description></item><item><title>Schema: Model</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/model/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/model/</guid><description>(v0.0.1)
Model kind: Model metadata: name: string labels: property1: string property2: string annotations: property1: string property2: string spec: runtime: dynlib: - path: string os: string arch: string variant: string libs: - string annotations: property1: string property2: string executable: - os: string arch: string libs: - string annotations: property1: string property2: string gateway: annotations: property1: string property2: string mcl: - path: string os: string arch: string variant: string libs: - string annotations: property1: string property2: string channels: - name: string alias: string expectedModelCount: 0 selectors: property1: string property2: string annotations: property1: string property2: string This schema object defines a Model kind.</description></item><item><title>Schema: Network</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/network/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/network/</guid><description>(v1.0.0)
Network kind: Network metadata: name: CAN1 annotations: message_lib: examples/stub/data/message.so function_lib: examples/stub/data/function.so spec: messages: - message: systemStatus annotations: struct_name: CAN1_systemStatus_t struct_size: 4 frame_id: 496 frame_length: 8 cycle_time_ms: 10 signals: - signal: Crc annotations: struct_member_name: crc struct_member_offset: 0 struct_member_primitive_type: uint8_t - signal: Alive annotations: struct_member_name: alive struct_member_offset: 1 struct_member_primitive_type: uint8 - signal: Temperature annotations: struct_member_name: temperature struct_member_offset: 2 struct_member_primitive_type: int16_t functions: encode: - function: counter_inc_uint8 annotations: position: 1 - function: crc_generate annotations: position: 0 decode: - function: crc_validate annotations: position: 0 A Network definition.</description></item><item><title>Schema: ParameterSet</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/parameterset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/parameterset/</guid><description>(v0.0.1)
ParameterSet kind: ParameterSet metadata: name: string labels: property1: string property2: string annotations: property1: string property2: string spec: parameters: - parameter: string value: string annotations: property1: string property2: string A parameter_set definition.
Properties Name Type Required Description kind string true none metadata object false Information relating to an object. » name string false The name of the object. » labels object false Identifying information used to identify objects within the system (e.</description></item><item><title>Schema: Propagator</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/propagator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/propagator/</guid><description>(v0.0.1)
Propagator kind: Propagator metadata: name: string labels: property1: string property2: string annotations: property1: string property2: string spec: options: direction: both signals: - signal: string target: string encoding: linear: min: 0 max: 0 factor: 0 offset: 0 mapping: - name: string source: 0 target: 0 range: min: 0 max: 0 A propagator definition.
Properties Name Type Required Description kind string true none metadata object false Information relating to an object. » name string false The name of the object.</description></item><item><title>Schema: Runnable</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/runnable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/runnable/</guid><description>(v1.0.0)
Runnable kind: Runnable metadata: name: target annotations: target_lib: examples/stub/lib/target.so spec: tasks: - function: task_init schedule: 0 - function: task_5ms schedule: 5 - function: task_10ms schedule: 10 - function: task_20ms schedule: 20 - function: task_40ms schedule: 40 A Runnable definition.
Supported annotations: Annotation Description target_lib Relative path of the shared library containing the Runnable library. Properties Name Type Required Description kind string true none metadata object false Information relating to an object.</description></item><item><title>Schema: SignalData</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/signaldata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/signaldata/</guid><description>(v0.0.1)
SignalData Data = [[0..N],[0..N]] MsgPack encoded Signal Data. Number of elements in each nested array should be identical.
Properties oneOf
Name Type Required Description anonymous SignalUid false Signal UID. xor
Name Type Required Description anonymous SignalValueNumeric false Numeric signal value. The value may be encoded as any integer or float type. xor
Name Type Required Description anonymous SignalValueBinary false Binary signal value. SignalUid 0 Signal UID.
Properties Name Type Required Description anonymous integer(int32) false Signal UID.</description></item><item><title>Schema: SignalGroup</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/signalgroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/signalgroup/</guid><description>(v0.0.1)
SignalGroup kind: SignalGroup metadata: name: string labels: property1: string property2: string annotations: property1: string property2: string spec: signals: - signal: string annotations: property1: string property2: string A signal group definition.
Properties Name Type Required Description kind string true none metadata object false Information relating to an object. » name string false The name of the object. » labels object false Identifying information used to identify objects within the system (e.</description></item><item><title>Schema: Stack</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/schemas/yaml/stack/</guid><description>(v0.0.1)
Stack kind: Stack metadata: name: string labels: property1: string property2: string annotations: property1: string property2: string spec: connection: timeout: string transport: redis: uri: string timeout: 0 runtime: env: property1: string property2: string stacked: true models: - name: string uid: 0 annotations: property1: string property2: string model: name: string mcl: strategy: string models: - name: string runtime: env: property1: string property2: string files: - string x32: true channels: - name: string alias: string expectedModelCount: 0 selectors: property1: string property2: string annotations: property1: string property2: string A stack definition.</description></item></channel></rss>