<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Model on Dynamic Simulation Environment</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/tags/model/</link><description>Recent content in Model on Dynamic Simulation Environment</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/tags/model/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Model - CSV</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/csv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/csv/</guid><description>Synposis A model for setting simulation signals with values read from a CSV file.
Model Structure examples/csv └── sim ├── data │ └── simulation.yml └── model └── input └── lib/libcsv.so └── data └── model.yml └── valueset.csv &amp;lt;-- CSV File. CSV File Timestamp;A;B;C 0.0000;1.0;2.0;3.0 0.0005;-1.1;2.1;3.1 0.0010;1.2;-2.2;3.2 0.0015;1.3;2.3;-3.3 Examples Simulation / DSE Script simulation channel physical uses dse.modelc https://github.com/boschglobal/dse.modelc v2.1.32 model input dse.modelc.csv channel physical signal_channel envar CSV_FILE model/input/data/valueset.csv file valueset.csv input.csv Simulation / Stack --- kind: Stack metadata: name: csv_stack spec: connection: transport: redispubsub: uri: redis://localhost:6379 timeout: 60 models: - name: simbus model: name: simbus channels: - name: physical expectedModelCount: 1 - name: input uid: 42 model: name: dse.</description></item><item><title>Model - Lua Model/MCL</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/lua/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/lua/</guid><description>Synposis Run models written in Lua using the Lua Model Library and operated via the built-in Lua MCL (Model Compatibility Library).
Lua Model using the Lua Model Library and Lua MCL Interface function model_step() model:log_notice(&amp;#34;model_step() @ %f&amp;#34;, model:model_time()) -- Increment the counter signal. local counter = model.sv[&amp;#34;signal&amp;#34;].scalar[SIG_COUNTER] counter = counter + 1 model.sv[&amp;#34;signal&amp;#34;].scalar[SIG_COUNTER] = counter -- Indicate success. return 0 end Model Structure examples/lua/model └── sim ├── data │ └── simulation.</description></item><item><title>FMI Gateway FMU</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/fmi/fmigateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/fmi/fmigateway/</guid><description>Synposis FMI Gateway FMU
Simulation Setup Structure Example Simulation Setup DOC: Provide description of Gateway Taskfile workflows.
Operation The configuration and operation of the gateway is done in the stack.yaml that is to be loaded by the gateway. The stack follows the following schema with some additional, gateway specific annotations/ additions.
Stack Metadata Name Type Required Description metadata object true none » name string true This field is required to be named &amp;ldquo;gateway&amp;rdquo; » annotation object false none »» start_redis boolean true Set to false with no redis instance should be started on windows, can be controlled via environment variable »» create_logfiles boolean false Set to true to create Logfiles of the started models, can be controlled via environment variable »» show_redis boolean false Set to true if the redis process should be shown as terminal window, can be controlled via environment variable »» show_simbus boolean false Set to true if the simbus process should be shown as terminal window, can be controlled via environment variable »» show_models boolean false Set to true if the model processes should be shown as terminal windows, can be controlled via environment variable »» model_stack string false Name of the Stack.</description></item><item><title>FMI Model Compatibility Library</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/fmi/fmimcl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/fmi/fmimcl/</guid><description>Synposis FMI Model Compatibility Library
Simulation Setup Structure Example Simulation Setup DOC: Provide description of FMI MCL Taskfile workflows.
Operation Measurement The FMI MCL can be configured to produce an MDF measurement file for scalar signals of the FMUs interface, including FMI Variables with &amp;rsquo;local&amp;rsquo; causality.
Note: the path of the measurement file is relative to the simulation path (i.e. /sim/&amp;hellip;).
# Using Simer; enable measurement on the FMU represented by &amp;#39;fmu_inst&amp;#39;.</description></item><item><title>FMI ModelC FMU</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/fmi/fmimodelc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/fmi/fmimodelc/</guid><description>Synposis FMI ModelC FMU
Simulation Setup Structure Example Simulation FMU Setup DOC: Provide description of FMI ModelC FMU Taskfile workflows.
FMU Operation DOC: Operation.</description></item></channel></rss>