<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Architecture Documents on Dynamic Simulation Environment</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/arch/</link><description>Recent content in Architecture Documents on Dynamic Simulation Environment</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/arch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Signal Vectors</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/arch/signalvector/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/arch/signalvector/</guid><description>Synopsis The Dynamic Simulation Environment (DSE) presents models with a simple vector interface for the exchange of signals. Those signals can be either:
scalar : Internally represented as a 64bit storage container (double). These values are transparently exchanged between models. Models may cast/convert these scalar values to other types as required. binary : Binary strings, which may container embedded NULL values, can be exchanged between models. Additionally a binary signal may be annotated with a MIME type which describes the content of a binary signal.</description></item><item><title>Gateway Models</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/arch/gateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/arch/gateway/</guid><description>Synopsis The Dynamic Simulation Environment (DSE) provides a Gateway API which can be used to connect remote simulations, via a gateway model, to a running DSE simulation. A gateway model takes care of signal exchange and time synchronisation between the remote simulation and the DSE simulation. Signals can be either scalar values or binary strings, the latter enabling virtual bus connections between simulation environments.
The gateway model runs in the remote simulation, and is written in that systems native language (or modelling construct).</description></item></channel></rss>