<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FMI - FMI Models on Dynamic Simulation Environment</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/fmi/</link><description>Recent content in FMI - FMI Models on Dynamic Simulation Environment</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/fmi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FMI Gateway FMU</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/fmi/fmigateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/fmi/fmigateway/</guid><description>Synposis FMI Gateway FMU
Simulation Setup Structure Example Simulation Setup DOC: Provide description of Gateway Taskfile workflows.
Operation The configuration and operation of the gateway is done in the stack.yaml that is to be loaded by the gateway. The stack follows the following schema with some additional, gateway specific annotations/ additions.
Stack Metadata Name Type Required Description metadata object true none » name string true This field is required to be named &amp;ldquo;gateway&amp;rdquo; » annotation object false none »» start_redis boolean true Set to false with no redis instance should be started on windows, can be controlled via environment variable »» create_logfiles boolean false Set to true to create Logfiles of the started models, can be controlled via environment variable »» show_redis boolean false Set to true if the redis process should be shown as terminal window, can be controlled via environment variable »» show_simbus boolean false Set to true if the simbus process should be shown as terminal window, can be controlled via environment variable »» show_models boolean false Set to true if the model processes should be shown as terminal windows, can be controlled via environment variable »» model_stack string false Name of the Stack.</description></item><item><title>FMI Model Compatibility Library</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/fmi/fmimcl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/fmi/fmimcl/</guid><description>Synposis FMI Model Compatibility Library
Simulation Setup Structure Example Simulation Setup DOC: Provide description of FMI MCL Taskfile workflows.
Operation Measurement The FMI MCL can be configured to produce an MDF measurement file for scalar signals of the FMUs interface, including FMI Variables with &amp;rsquo;local&amp;rsquo; causality.
Note: the path of the measurement file is relative to the simulation path (i.e. /sim/&amp;hellip;).
# Using Simer; enable measurement on the FMU represented by &amp;#39;fmu_inst&amp;#39;.</description></item><item><title>FMI ModelC FMU</title><link>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/fmi/fmimodelc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://boschglobal.github.io/dse.doc/docs/user/models/fmi/fmimodelc/</guid><description>Synposis FMI ModelC FMU
Simulation Setup Structure Example Simulation FMU Setup DOC: Provide description of FMI ModelC FMU Taskfile workflows.
FMU Operation DOC: Operation.</description></item></channel></rss>